As a Columbia University graduate, this is bringing me so much joy.
Early this morning, Columbia students have taken back our campus in the spirit of the 68th occupation of Hamilton Hall, establishing the RASA Solidarity Encampment on East Butler Lawn.
Their statement reads, Columbia University Apartheid Divest is a continuation of the Vietnam anti-war movement and the movement to divest from apartheid in South Africa.
As students at this institution, it is our responsibility to stand against our inherent complicity in genocide and ethnic cleansing from Palestine to Harlem.
We refuse to accept a world where the death of over 30,000 Palestinians is normal, acceptable or profitable.
We are in complete solidarity with the Palestinian people who resiliently resist decades of occupation, apartheid and genocide.
We remain steadfast in our commitment to see a free Palestine within our lifetime.
I'm crying.
We demand divestment.
The RASA Solidarity Encampment will remain until our demand is met.
Divest all of Columbia's finances, including the endowment, from companies and institutions that profit from Israeli apartheid, genocide and occupation in Palestine.
Ensure accountability by increasing transparency around financial investments.
This is the history of students at Columbia University.
This right here.
And I am so honored to be a part of that legacy.
And this is why the back of my robe read,
Masters in Revolution.
And this is why I am so honored to be a part of that legacy.